Max Maievskyi

+49-1517-261-04-06 | MaksymMaievskyi@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/maksym-maievskyi | github.com/RedMaxMay

Current Location: Hamburg, Germany

Summary

As a passionate Front-End Developer with a solid foundation in relevant technologies, I'm confident in my ability to add value to any development team. I want to apply my skills and knowledge to a full-time role as a Front-End Developer, where I can further develop my expertise and contribute to creating outstanding digital solutions. In addition to my technical skills, my decade of experience leading teams has increased my soft skills quite well, so I think I can contribute to the success of your company.

EDUCATION

Tel-Ran.de GmbH Aug 2022 – Jun 2023 React Frontend Developer Berlin, Germany Kyiv National University of FT Sep 2008 - Aug 2013 Master's degree, Human Resources Management and Economics Kyiv, Ukraine

EXPERIENCE

Head of Department / Front-end Developer

Jan 2019 - Feb 2022Kyiv, Ukraine

Art Expert LLC

- Continued as a department manager, leading a team of 12 people
- · Automated and optimized the department's work to achieve flawless results
- Learned HTML, CSS, and JS to create new e-commerce websites to grow the company
- Worked in a team to develop 2 e-commerce websites, a CRM, and a CMS:
 - * Collaborated with the team to design UI/UX
 - * Participated in the development of main pages, catalogs with sorting, shopping carts, and product pages and optimized everything for mobile devices (HTML, CSS, JS, Git, RestAPI).

Head of Department Nov 2014 - Jan 2019 Kyiv, Ukraine

Art Expert LLC

• Expanded the company and created a new department

- Increased sales and profitability by over 200% in 3 years
- Managed a team of 10 people (set goals, monitored task completion, trained and analyzed department performance, etc.)
- Developed strategies to increase company profitability, optimized workflows, and proposed new ideas for growth

Designer-Manager Jul 2013 - Nov 2014

Art Expert LLC

Kyiv, Ukraine

- Developed design solutions in Photoshop and Illustrator
- Expanded the company's client base through direct consultations and sales
- Contributed to the successful implementation of projects for restaurants and hotels
- Coordinated with the production department (created task lists and received completed work)

My Pet projects

"Green Shop" | React SPA. E-commerce plants store

github.com/RedMaxMay/greenshop

• Semantic HTML5 markup, CSS custom properties, CSS Grid, Flexbox, Responsive Design, Axios, LocalStorage, React, React Router, React Hooks, CSS modules, REST API, Redux Toolkit

"Countries" | React SPA. REST Countries API

github.com/RedMaxMay/countries

• Mobile-first workflow, React - JS library, Styled Components - For styles, Semantic HTML5 markup, CSS custom properties, Flexbox, CSS Grid, Responsive Design, Axios, REST API, React Router v6, React Icons

"Pages" | React SPA. Online book store

github.com/RedMaxMay/book

• Responsive Design, Semantic HTML5 markup, CSS custom properties, CSS Grid, Flexbox, React, React Router, React Hooks, CSS modules

SKILLS

Technical skills: React, Redux, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TpeScript, Responsive Design, Material UI, REST API, MySQL, Git, Photoshop, Illustrator, UX/UI design

Soft skills: My experience as a team manager has helped me develop strong skills in leadership, communication, and problem-solving.

Languages: English (B1-B2), Ukrainian (native), Russian (native)